{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993360024","data":{"timestamp":" 946993360024"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993364233","data":{"timestamp":" 946993364233"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993369028","data":{"timestamp":" 946993369028"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993380845","data":{"timestamp":" 946993380844"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993391135","data":{"timestamp":" 946993391135"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993397568","data":{"timestamp":" 946993397568"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993403711","data":{"timestamp":" 946993403711"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993407885","data":{"timestamp":" 946993407885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993412103","data":{"timestamp":" 946993412103"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993417300","data":{"timestamp":" 946993417300"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993421807","data":{"timestamp":" 946993421807"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993426008","data":{"timestamp":" 946993426008"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993431896","data":{"timestamp":" 946993431895"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993436156","data":{"timestamp":" 946993436156"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993440748","data":{"timestamp":" 946993440748"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993446234","data":{"timestamp":" 946993446234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993450963","data":{"timestamp":" 946993450963"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993455811","data":{"timestamp":" 946993455811"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993460207","data":{"timestamp":" 946993460207"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993467297","data":{"timestamp":" 946993467296"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993473952","data":{"timestamp":" 946993473952"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993479823","data":{"timestamp":" 946993479823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993488829","data":{"timestamp":" 946993488829"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993495272","data":{"timestamp":" 946993495271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993500913","data":{"timestamp":" 946993500912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993506681","data":{"timestamp":" 946993506680"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 2fd26dc8-09b9-4fcd-8457-54417d9e04a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993527015","data":{"timestamp":" 946993527015"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993527269","data":{"timestamp":" 946993527269"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993528579","data":{"timestamp":" 946993528579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993528920","data":{"timestamp":" 946993528919"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993530076","data":{"timestamp":" 946993530076"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993530374","data":{"timestamp":" 946993530373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993530663","data":{"timestamp":" 946993530663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993539730","data":{"timestamp":" 946993539730"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993541227","data":{"timestamp":" 946993541227"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993553918","data":{"timestamp":" 946993553918"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993554173","data":{"timestamp":" 946993554173"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993558417","data":{"timestamp":" 946993558417"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993563529","data":{"timestamp":" 946993563529"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993565655","data":{"timestamp":" 946993565655"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993569831","data":{"timestamp":" 946993569831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993571779","data":{"timestamp":" 946993571779"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993577613","data":{"timestamp":" 946993577613"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993581321","data":{"timestamp":" 946993581321"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993581585","data":{"timestamp":" 946993581585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993581823","data":{"timestamp":" 946993581823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993584545","data":{"timestamp":" 946993584545"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993586764","data":{"timestamp":" 946993586764"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993591434","data":{"timestamp":" 946993591433"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993593339","data":{"timestamp":" 946993593339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993593612","data":{"timestamp":" 946993593612"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993605093","data":{"timestamp":" 946993605093"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993610204","data":{"timestamp":" 946993610204"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993617493","data":{"timestamp":" 946993617493"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993619475","data":{"timestamp":" 946993619474"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 49efd34f-d6bf-4573-82b9-1c868d2dab3e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993636648","data":{"timestamp":" 946993636648"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993641797","data":{"timestamp":" 946993641797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993650194","data":{"timestamp":" 946993650194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993657015","data":{"timestamp":" 946993657015"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993683906","data":{"timestamp":" 946993683906"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993688979","data":{"timestamp":" 946993688979"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993694658","data":{"timestamp":" 946993694658"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993698732","data":{"timestamp":" 946993698732"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993702253","data":{"timestamp":" 946993702253"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993706661","data":{"timestamp":" 946993706661"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993718760","data":{"timestamp":" 946993718760"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993728097","data":{"timestamp":" 946993728097"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993732701","data":{"timestamp":" 946993732701"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993737357","data":{"timestamp":" 946993737357"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993744391","data":{"timestamp":" 946993744391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993750224","data":{"timestamp":" 946993750224"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993814186","data":{"timestamp":" 946993814186"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993862458","data":{"timestamp":" 946993862457"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993867956","data":{"timestamp":" 946993867956"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993885275","data":{"timestamp":" 946993885274"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993900346","data":{"timestamp":" 946993900346"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993907303","data":{"timestamp":" 946993907302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993917541","data":{"timestamp":" 946993917541"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993922376","data":{"timestamp":" 946993922376"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993929735","data":{"timestamp":" 946993929735"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993947087","data":{"timestamp":" 946993947087"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993952398","data":{"timestamp":" 946993952398"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993958085","data":{"timestamp":" 946993958085"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993962332","data":{"timestamp":" 946993962332"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993966375","data":{"timestamp":" 946993966375"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993970682","data":{"timestamp":" 946993970682"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993979394","data":{"timestamp":" 946993979394"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993985167","data":{"timestamp":" 946993985165"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993993577","data":{"timestamp":" 946993993577"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994001719","data":{"timestamp":" 946994001719"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 7d1849d6-b394-4a10-87be-8b4277bca1bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994014956","data":{"timestamp":" 946994014956"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 5622ac2e-4c28-4fb5-b927-df882a2e815e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994022514","data":{"timestamp":" 946994022514"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 5622ac2e-4c28-4fb5-b927-df882a2e815e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994033876","data":{"timestamp":" 946994033876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 5622ac2e-4c28-4fb5-b927-df882a2e815e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994050700","data":{"timestamp":" 946994050700"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 5622ac2e-4c28-4fb5-b927-df882a2e815e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994098074","data":{"timestamp":" 946994098073"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 5622ac2e-4c28-4fb5-b927-df882a2e815e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994114383","data":{"timestamp":" 946994114382"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000104_164226"," gameId":" 5622ac2e-4c28-4fb5-b927-df882a2e815e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}